webnewswire.com 2006-03-21

# webnewswire.com - Privacy Policy

Our site respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use it. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). 

**Posting stories**  
When you send us stories and inputs, you agree to give us non-exclusive copyright to the material without any royalty or necessity of accrediting you with any byline. You also agree that you are the original author of the material and you are not infringing on anyone else's intellectual property. In case of any violation, we will be free to share your contact and ISP information for any such claims. You also agree to bear all legal complications that may originate due to your posting, and hold us harmless. In case you disagree with any of these clauses then kindly do not submit any stories. 

If you think that your story has been posted by someone in error then please contact us through the feedback form, and we will delete the story immediately. Please note that there are sometimes hundreds of stories published each day and most of them originate from submissions by users. 

**Our site and Cookies**  
Upon your first visit to Our site, Our site sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. Our site uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. Our site does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people search. Our site will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the site may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
Our site does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. Our site notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users. For example, we may use your IP address or browser language to determine which language to use when showing search results or advertisements. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
The sites displayed or linked to our site are developed by people over whom we exercise no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. 

**With Whom Does Our site Share Information?**  
Our site may share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. 

**Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy**  
We may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

For any questions, please fill in the feedback form.
